[Music]
What is the doctor saying? Why did you ask me? I
had an operation last week that cost five lakh rupees. I will have another operation
this week. I will have another operation and it will cost
another five lakh rupees. I don't know
what to do.
What kind of health insurance did
you put in? What
kind of nothing did you do? Brother, shouldn't you have taken a health insurance? All the money you have saved up with hard work will be spent only when you go to the hospital. What is the beauty of health insurance? I have forgotten about it. Now I think I should take a health insurance myself. What kind of
a good health
insurance policy can benefit the middle class or the poor?
Brother, let me tell you a good policy. I am
giving you a policy like the one you asked for at ICICI Bank. Now, if you
have seen it, for example, a
health insurance company in the top 10  If a
husband and wife between the ages of 21 and 25 take a policy for just ₹3
lakh in the health insurance, if you
look at the approximate cost, it will cost them ₹10,000 to ₹
15,000 per year,
but if you look at the coverage of ₹25 lakh for the same age
in ICI Bank, it will cost
just ₹
6,556 per year.
Tell me yourself, brother, where is 3 lakh,
where is 20 lakh?
I am reading the list one by one. See for
yourself. The name of that health policy is
Health Shield
360. This policy is only available to those who have an ICI Bank account. If
not, is it a special offer only for those who have a
credit card in ICI Bank?
They will give this policy to people from a young
child to 60 years old.
10 lakhs to 15 lakhs.  They have given a list of premiums according to age from 20 25 50
75 lakhs to 1 crore rupees.
Brother, this is the
list. Check it yourself according to your age and the members in your house.
Brother, I will
only read the first line and then I will
give you this list. You can
join whichever policy you like according to your age. Brother, first of all, if
an
individual between the ages of 21 and 25 takes a policy for 25 lakh rupees, if you
see how much it will cost him,
it will be ₹5090 per year. If he takes a policy for ₹50 lakh rupees, it will
be ₹5799. If he takes a policy for 75 lakh rupees, it will
cost him 6870. Similarly, if he takes a
policy for ₹1 crore rupees, it will
cost him 7296 per year.  If an individual between the
ages of 21 and 25 and
one child
take a policy for Rs 25 lakhs per year, the
cost per year would be
6556 If it were 50 lakhs, the cost would be
7701 If it were 75 lakhs, the cost would be 8848 If it were
1 crore, the cost would be
9938 If it were an individual between the ages of 21 and 25
plus
two children take a
health insurance policy for Rs 25 lakhs
per year, the cost would be
7828 If it were 50 lakhs, the cost would be
9195 If it were 75 lakhs, the cost would be
10656 If it were 1 crore, the cost would be
11221 If it were a
husband and wife between the ages of 21 and 25  If you take
a policy for both of you, it will cost
₹7469 per year for a coverage of ₹25 lakhs. If
you look at the coverage of ₹50 lakhs, it
will cost ₹8773. If you look at the coverage of ₹75 lakhs, it will cost
₹1080. If
you look at the coverage of ₹1 crore, it will cost ₹10706 per year.
Similarly, if you look at the coverage of
₹25 lakhs for a husband and wife between the ages of 21 and 25 and one child, it will
cost
₹9946. If you look at the coverage of ₹50 lakhs, it will cost
₹11683. If you look at the coverage of ₹
75 lakhs, it will cost ₹
13423. If you look at the coverage of ₹1 crore, it will cost ₹14257. Similarly, if you look at the coverage of ₹25 lakhs for a
husband and
wife plus two children between the ages of 21 and 25, it will
cost ₹13016 on average. Similarly, if you look at the coverage of ₹50 lakhs, it will cost ₹10016 on average.  It
costs ₹15289 per rupee, and
₹17567 per year for 75 lakh rupees.
If you look at ₹1 crore rupees, it
costs ₹18658 per year.
Similarly, there are policies for 10 lakh, 15 lakh, and 20
lakh rupees.
Look at this table and choose the
coverage you need according to your age. You can choose the
policy and take it.
I will go to ICICI Bank today and
take the policy you mentioned immediately.